https://www.delarue.com/privacy

Public Education
Operational Excellence (SPW)
Contact
Samoan 10 Tala Commemorative note on SAFEGUARD®, with Gemini™
Privacy
Who we are
The pages on the website (“the Website”) are published by De La Rue plc, a company registered in England and Wales with company registration number 3834125, whose registered address is at De La Rue House, Jays Close, Viables, Basingstoke, Hampshire RG22 4BS.
De La Rue plc respect your right to privacy and will process personal information you provide only in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation, Data Protection Act 2018, the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 and other applicable privacy laws.
The information collected and how it is used
De La Rue will not collect any information about individuals, except where it is specifically and knowingly provided by them.
When you visit De La Rue plc’s Website, De La Rue’s web server collects some basic information such as your browser type, IP address, internet service provider’s domain name, which pages you accessed on the site, and when. Details of cookies that De La Rue uses on the Website can be found on the Cookie notice.
De La Rue plc use this information to provide you with and maintain the quality of the Website and to analyse the use of the Website in order to help guide improvements. Personally identifiable information is not automatically collected.
If you register for the alert service, you will need to provide your name and email address. This information will be held by De La Rue. The information will not be used for any other purpose; it will be stored securely and will not be shared with third parties. By registering for the alerts, you consent to this use of your name and email address.
Third-party use of information
Except as described above, De La Rue plc will not disclose, sell or rent your personal information to any third party unless you have consented to this. If you do consent but later change your mind, you may contact De La Rue plc (as appropriate) to ask for any such activity to stop.
However, if a third party acquires all (or substantially all) of De La Rue plc's business and/or assets, De La Rue plc (as applicable) may disclose your personal information to that third party in connection with the acquisition. De La Rue plc may also disclose your personal information where required to do so by applicable law, by a governmental body or by a law enforcement agency.
Finally, De La Rue plc may also collect anonymised details about visitors to the Website for the purposes of aggregate statistics or reporting purposes. However, no single individual will be identifiable from the anonymised details collected for these purposes.
International transfers
De La Rue plc may transfer personal information that is collected from you to third-party data processors located in countries that are outside of the European Economic Area in connection with the above purposes. Please be aware that countries which are outside the European Economic Area may not offer the same level of data protection as the United Kingdom, although the collection, storage and use of your personal data will continue to be governed by this privacy policy.
Security
Whilst De La Rue plc take appropriate technical and organisational measures to safeguard the personal information that you provide, no transmission over the Internet can ever be guaranteed secure. Consequently, please note that the security of any personal information that you transfer over the Internet to De La Rue plc cannot be guaranteed.
Your rights
You have the following rights:
the right to be provided with copies of personal information that De La Rue plc hold about you at any time, subject to a fee specified by law;
the right to ask De La Rue plc to update and correct any out-of-date or incorrect personal information held about you free of charge; and
the right to opt out of any marketing communications that De La Rue plc (or any third party to whom they have disclosed your personal information with your consent) may send you.
If you wish to exercise any of the above rights, please write to De La Rue plc (as appropriate) at the address specified above.
Connect with us:
Connect with us:
© De La Rue plc 2020
